Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/erick-ruo-6872ab1b4 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Team Development
Independence
C (Programming Language)

Certifications

Git for system administration
Certificate of completion Laravel
Developer

Building RESTful APIs in Laravel Laravel 6 Essential Training: Testing, Securing and Deploying Apps

Building Laravel and Vue.js Web Apps

Erick Ruo

Software engineer

Nairobi County, Kenya

Summary

Experienced Android Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in Firebase, SQL, and Java. Strong engineering professional pursuing a Bachelors of Science in Computer Science focused in Computer Software Engineering at Kibabii University.

Experience

Watoto Coding
Web Developer(volunteer)
December 2022 - Present (1 year 6 months)

Android Developer January 2022 - December 2022 (1 year) Bungoma, Kenya

Education

Kibabii University

Bachelor Degree of Computer Science, Computer Science (2020 - 2024)

Gaitu High School

Certificate, Human Resources Management/Personnel Administration, General · (February 2016 - September 2020)